Derren Brown: Pushed to the Edge is a documentary, tv
movie film directed by Jon Richards.
Derren Brown investigates the power of social compliance by persuading an unwitting member
of the public into believing that they have pushed someone to their death.
Himself, played by Derren Brown.
Tom, played by Tom Carter.
Himself, played by Chris Kingston.
Herself, played by Heather Ashley Chase.
Himself, played by Matt Lucas.
Himself, played by Martin Freeman.
The various stage and television shows performed by the
psychological illusionist Derren Brown.
The film explores themes of psychology,
manipulation, deception, social engineering.